<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logan Corrente</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Logan Corrente</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Developer Journal</title>
      <link>/projects/cse110-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/cse110-journal/</guid>
      <description>In spring of 2024 I decided to sign up for Professor Powell&amp;rsquo;s CSE 110, Software Engineering course at UCSD. With a hectic start and not enough chairs in one of the biggest lecture halls on campus, we started the course.
We were put into teams, and my team became Team Tungsten. This included myself and 10 other students.
The task we had been given was to create developer journal app on top of exams, long lectures, and some PAs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Room Scheduling App</title>
      <link>/projects/room-scheduling-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/room-scheduling-app/</guid>
      <description>While working for UCSD IT services, I met someone who needed help rewriting an app that he made for room scheduling. I was quite interested and spent most of my time at ITS working on this project.
This is a frame of one of the actual hosted carousel pages. He had many pages like this that were created by a local designer and hosted through Carousel. These pages displayed any information and were hosted on a separate server to ensure the devices just needed to display the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QI Check in System</title>
      <link>/projects/checkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/checkin/</guid>
      <description>Link to the repo
Upon arriving to UC San Diego, I decided to start looking for student jobs to keep myself afloat while in school. I ended up getting a job at a new developing makerspace in the Qualcomm Institute on campus.
After a few weeks of 3d printing, laser cutting and learning some woodworking and metalworking, I was given the task of continuing a project that my boss had started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA L&#39;Space Mission Concept Academy</title>
      <link>/projects/mission-concept-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/mission-concept-academy/</guid>
      <description>Link to our Preliminary Design Review
As a kid I absolutely loved space, technology and science&amp;ndash;particularly space exploration. This led to a great curiosity and a new dream to work for a space company.
Before transferring to University I was looking for any and every opportunity to get ahead, and one of my computer science classmates gave a presentation on a mission concept academy she did with NASA L&amp;rsquo;Space and that night I went home and applied to the program.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
